Jhal
scientist very good evening good evening
friend or behavior vagina kasana and
anuraag purusha bhusara this is only mission and
mission possible VR box with now more
interesting questions for all of you are you can
participate in the more exciting
prizes let's start with Ashraf first
and last question it will ask sw0
question ghee online screen so that you can see it's
Appamma reader for your support are
you alone or two wheeler which you can use
rally will user name motor insurance option
- comprehensive inch and from this this third
party insurance not really necessary and
last question
109 sonth rob last question of the day
shift in comment participated with awesome
unique voice friends can claim your family
members par hum and participate and this so that you people hum log ne bataye tha morning me ki hum log daily basis par aapko five questions in every
two and hum log
aapko five  We will give more questions and you have to answer these in an
interesting part. You can
participate and answer all five questions
and you can be able to win the prize. It is
not that if you
participate in the competition, you cannot participate in the competition
or
you cannot get prizes for the Sikh Authority on the First Cup
at any cost because in the common man
form gives less price. So I
request you to please participate in this competition
with your friends in the form
that has developed like this and China Sainik
Vihar. Creating awareness regarding road
safety, change cannot happen with one person,
we all should take this thing forward together
and we would request you to encourage
everyone else to participate in the Boring Scars so they
also have a chance to
win it and as you can see, the link
which is there for me will be there,
now you can go to that link and click on the answer and
give your answer. You can
also go to our YouTube webpage and answer your question.  You
can answer it, it will remain a
ballot till now, you come friend, I will put your entries,
after that it will not be proved there
and the time and place of every question is
for you and the result of all these,
from our morning and till now, the result of all
these questions, you
can see it on our
evening show,
our show Looteron Clock, on that our
results will be run out, enemy email
plant, speaking and by going there you
can see your results of who has
won the prize, we will normalize your results on our webpage, on that
also on our Facebook account and
on our YouTube channel, but the only
request is that if you
come to the tempered glass show and can
see your results yourself, can see the questions, choose only
on screen, suppose you own a
novel two-wheeler, which you can use, will mean
thick inches and this option, yes
comprehensive insurance secure third
Party Insurance C9
first necessary storm I don't know please come
and join with others and give your answers
and cheer up for exciting prizes which if you can see
online quiz
contest van omni price everyday you can
become a part of rolls happy
and win exciting prizes every day
like helmet for kids an absolute
tips health benefits for your family to it's
really interesting and we
can write it further and this whole
champion is related to and Russia is you you
promote road safety hai
jhal so
as you saw that this is free every day
road safety virus important guava
tv basically road safety is what is
our theme today which is BSP question actually on
daily basis we will talk to
you on which we will talk to you related to
road safety knowledge ki jyoti phuse
topic so we will talk to you related to this so
today as you know this is our
first so force day we will talk to you about zonal
road safety  We will talk about it and these questions have been given to
you related to it only.
If you look closely, all the
other questions that we had before were also
related to normal road safety and this one is
also a question related to road safety.
So, road safety is
not for anyone else. Road
safety
regulations are for us,
how can we make our day safer
and how can we make our day better. So, these are the
rules and
regulations that should not be followed because
we are a traffic policeman
or you are not for others, these are for
us, for our safety, for the safety of our loved ones.
As important as
your family members are for you, you are equally important for
them. So,
make your day for yourself and for them only. You have to follow these very important road safety
rules.
As you all know, every day is
not for one person; it is
for everyone.  Somewhere or the other, on a daily
basis, we are connected to our roads
because sometimes you have to go somewhere, to the market,
if you are a housewife, then she has to go to her mother's house,
here she has to go to her relatives'
house or you have to go to the office,
here she has to come back, so somewhere or the other
we are connected to our roads, either we are
typing or trying to attack, or
riding a bike, or going to tube
wells, or even if we are like a per different thing and
using it,
somewhere or the other we are
connected to those roads, so it is our
own responsibility that we can
make that road safe for our readers and for others,
so if we adopt these small tricks, then
somewhere or the other we
can make our roads safe, so you people also become a
part of this campaign, join us
and we, we should participate in this
and have made an important contribution in making our roads safe, it has happened that the
girls had made a
video of Ajay Loot Lo in
English
The question is when you
go to the date screen, you guys click on the link and answer it,
Ajay had gone behind,
so do you know somewhere or the other we all
know what are the road safety rules and
why and we should follow them,
it is for our own safety
but we ourselves do
not follow them every day, that is,
if we have to
go somewhere nearby then we
wear the helmet saying that it is for a short while or we do
not wear a helmet and if we do not wear a helmet then we do not wear a helmet,
so it is very
important for relationships, if you are
going anywhere, as soon as you use a two wheeler then
you should wear a helmet, if you are
going by car then it is very important to wear
slippers late at night,
here you are not spending print, so
you leave it and
you provide them
and type them, either you
can book or you can choose any other
option  You can do it madam because if
you try this, that is, if you drive recklessly, then
somewhere you
can put your life as well as someone else's life in danger,
so change these small things in your life a
little bit and somewhere you will stop being
careless,
because if we understand
that our carelessness can
become the reason for someone else's death,
if we leave that carelessness, then somewhere it
can only make their anger worse,
they request you to join this campaign,
join us to make your anger better and be a part of this campaign
because when we change, the country will change, China
starts with this app, which is the question that will be
presented and
raw screen, so maximum number of people should come
and participate in it, next to this will be
for today only, the alarm will be
set later, it will not be of any use to you,
I have a question for you, laugh on your face, that is the issue
on all twelve which you used,
will still need motor insurance
first  Here's sister St. John's Chiefs
Third Party Insurance See Not Really It's Really Not
No 1956 If you know any answers,
Pimple, then you come and join this
campaign and I will tell you my answer sheet
and you have a chance to win exciting prizes,
you can see its results,
our show comes in the night now the last
speaking is at 10 pm, so your
results there will be unknowns, request
you to can also come, you can see your
results and view more exciting
excited to Delhi all results, your
most welcome to win exciting prizes,
you can participate and monitoring you can
participate in each question like 5
questions Delhi, so you can participate
and all of you can win prizes, will
request to come and join that,
leave the question a page on screen finally came
onto your answers, you
can also go to our YouTube channel and buy with your tears,
our Om Joe  We can also go behind that and
give our answers and give ourselves a
chance to win this,
thank you so much, you were listening otherwise you have to take a
specific agreement to
participate in this work in the most exciting
prizes, thank you to everyone.